americansforthearts.org 2019-06-13

# Americans for the Arts Privacy Statement | Americans for the Arts

_Updated: May 2018_

##  Overall

Your privacy while visiting our site is important to us. Because we gather certain types of information about the users of our site, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it.

##  Information We Collect

Americans for the Arts collects the following types of personal information: names (individual and organization), titles, postal and e-mail addresses, phone and fax numbers, and billing information. We use this information to reply to inquiries and process billing and business requests related to program participation, including listservs, membership, donations, purchases, and online communications. This information will only be accessed by appropriate Americans for the Arts staff and the occasional third party as described below. Basic contact information collected, excluding e-mail address will be shared via roster to all meeting attendees and meeting exhibitors. To suppress your contact information from being included in any meeting roster e-mail us. Americans for the Arts, like many nonprofits, occasionally rents its postal address lists to carefully selected like-minded organizations. To suppress your name and address from these lists, please e-mail us and place "Suppress Mail List Rental" in the subject line and include your Name and Address in the body.

When you submit information via web forms, it is used to provide you with services which you have requested from us. By submitting data via web forms on our website(s), you consent to share your data in accordance with the guidelines of this privacy statement. If you require information about the data we've collected to process your online request please [e-mail us](mailto:webmaster@artsusa.org) for information.

##  Cookies

Cookies are text messages stored on your computer's hard drive. The message is sent back to a website's server each time your browser requests a page from the server that set the cookie. The main purposes of our cookies are to prepare customized Web pages that the user has requested, to let users move as quickly and easily around our site as possible, and to identify users who have voluntarily submitted any personal information about themselves to us. We use temporary session cookies that only apply to the current site visit, with the exception of our statistics software that is permanent (to identify repeat users). These cookies only contain technical information and can be deleted from your hard drive or denied if you have disabled the cookies without affecting site performance. Information submitted to us confidentially will not be shared with outside organizations, individuals, or companies, and users are free to delete cookies from their computers' hard drives at any time. Most features that AmericansForTheArts.org provides can still be utilized if you have disabled cookies in your browser, but they may require you to log-in multiple times and may otherwise affect site performance. If you prefer not to allow cookies turn them off in our browser by following the instructions found in your borwser support:

##  Information Collected and Stored Automatically

As you browse through the website, read pages, or download information, we may gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. We may automatically collect and store only the following information about your visit: The Internet domain (for example, "xcompany.com" if you use a private Internet access account or "yourschool.edu" if you connect from a university's domain) and IP address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web) from which you access our website; the type of browser and operating system used to access our site; the date and time you access our site; the pages you visit; and if you linked to the Americans for the Arts site from another website, the address of that website. We use this information to help us make our site more useful to visitors—to learn about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology our visitors use. We do not track or record information about individuals and their visits.

##  Material Fulfillment and Third Party Service Providers

To facilitate AmericansForTheArts.org's offerings and services, on occasion certain selected user information must be made temporarily available to selected data processors such as fulfillment bureaus or database consultants. Such data processors are instructed to act strictly upon instruction from Americans for the Arts.

##  Links

This site contains links to other sites for which Americans for the Arts is not responsible in terms of the content or privacy practices of such sites. Americans for the Arts encourages you to review the privacy policies of the sites that you visit, especially before submitting your personal information.

##  Americans for the Arts Listservs

Americans for the Arts manages several listservs. Only those who have joined particular listservs may post to those lists. Americans for the Arts does not give, sell, or rent these lists' subscriber information to any third parties. However, please note that content sent to the list is viewable by all subscribers. If you'd like to unsubscribe from a listserv, please [contact us](mailto:memberships@artsusa.org).

##  How to Unsubscribe from Americans for the Arts E-mail Newsletters

To unsubscribe from receiving our e-newsletters, please [contact us](mailto:webmaster@artsusa.org), and we will remove your registration account.

##  How to Update Information

If you need to update your e-mail information or any other personal information, please [contact us](mailto:webmaster@artsusa.org).

##  Contact Information

For more information, requests, questions, or comments, please [e-mail us](mailto:webmaster@artsusa.org) or call us at 202.371.2830 or toll free at 1.866.471.ARTS.
